So everybody welcome to the first
episode of our dasha series. And so
today we're going to cover planet sun
dasha and what happens when you go
through this dasha whether sun is good
or bad in your horoscope. Now if you're
new to my channel check out this link
okay and this will tell you what dashas
are. They're far more important than
your early transits. Okay. Without them
yearly transits have no merit because of
the fact you know when you hear things
like uh uh people are having
I you know people say I had 10 years of
bad period in my life. I went through
the most miserable time of my life for
the past 20 years or the for the past 15
years. you know, in those past in those
15 years, you can't tell me that this
person didn't go through one good yearly
transit because his Jupiter might be
excelled at one year. His Mercury might
be excelled at one u at one point in the
year. Why is it that he didn't get what
he wanted? Why is it that his wishes
didn't get fulfilled? Because of the
fact he his major planetary time period
was bad. So when you read a book or go
on uh you know televisions and all watch
these television shows that says oh for
Gemini moon signs 2012 is going to be
the best year because it is going to
bring you marriage and wealth and then
nothing happens of that sort and then
you're left wondering you know what just
happened that's because of the fact your
transit or I mean your your plenary time
period of tasha is not good. So no
matter how good the planet is, it's
really not going to give that much of an
effect. So let's say for one person,
Jupiter is in the 11th house in uh in
2012 and it's excelled in cancer. Does
that mean he's going to get all the
gains he he wants? If he's going through
a bad planetary time period, it might
only give him 15%. Whatever he was
looking for in this taja period, okay?
Uh so in for example, if he was going to
get 10 pieces of bread in his taja
period, okay? But because of his dasha
being bad that Jupiter is only going to
give him two pieces of bread. But if he
was going through a good uh planetary
time uh good dasha and then Jupiter came
then it would have been like 10 out of
10. He would have gotten 10 breads or
nine breads. Or if he was going through
a good planetary time period of let's
say 10 years and then bad transits came
early. Instead of 10 breads he might get
eight breads. But guess what? It's far
better than two breads. And this is why
it's so important to know dashas more
than yearly transits. Okay. So let's
find out what happens when you go
through a sun dasha. And how do you know
if you're going through sundasha right
now or if you're going to be going
through the sundasha? Well, this is why
I did the whole nakhatra series. So
during your birth time when if your moon
was in utaka nakhatra utra pelguni and
utra ashida uttra ashila nakhatra if you
were born in any one of these three
constellations your your life started
with a six-year time period of sun maybe
four maybe three depending upon what
degree moon was in but you started your
life with a six-year time period of sun
and after that 10 years of moon then 7
years of Mars and Rahu and Jupiter and
all of So that's how this is how you
find out what plan time period you're
going through now which I actually
explained to you in my dasha video that
I did. So sasha it's quite easy to
determine what dashas are really about.
It's nothing it's not rocket science.
What does sun represents in your
horoscope? Your father figure
your vitality. Okay your soul.
The king meaning government,
politics,
government jobs,
your family business,
your father's legacy and your father's
health and including your own health,
your heart is represented by sun. So
let's cover what if sun is good in your
horoscope. What happens? Well, during
the six year time period of sun and
let's say you got this between your 20
and 26 years of age
wherever you were working you will get a
promotion. You will become let's say a
district manager. What is a district
manager? Somebody who is handling five,
six, seven different offices of a
business. Okay? And he's in charge of
all of them. Like the sun s is in charge
of all the planets around him. And this
is a good representation of the sun. You
you can become an executive. You can get
a government job that you were looking
for. Actually there usually government
jobs don't pay anymore that well. But
this relates to anything to do with the
government law. Government is law also.
So sun gives good inclination towards
the law field. You know if you're going
through law schooling your son and your
son is beautifully placed you'll be
graduating with honors. But again, you
know, this is a small piece of the
puzzle. You got to look at the whole
chart. So that's what sun does in your
good plenary time period. You know, you
get benefits from the government,
meaning that let's say you get a letter
one day from the IRS and you're like,
actually, that's how I would react. But
um you open that letter and it says,
"Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Smith. Um we
actually owe you $20,000 because we it
seems like we overcharged you for the
past 10 years." And there you go. You're
getting benefit from the government. If
you were looking for some government
assistant, grants, loans, you get those
in a good plenary time situation. You
also take up your family business. You
especially your father's business. Why?
Because father your family legacy is
mainly your father's legacy. So if let's
say your father has a business, um let's
say he sells medical equipments, you if
you're in that right age, you will take
over that business and you'll take that
business to new heights.
But what happens when sunshai is bad?
Okay, let's find that out. So let's say
if uh your sun is debilitated in your
horoscope or sitting with the north node
rahu per se during that six period uh
six uh year time period, you better be
careful first of all is not to cheat the
government out of anything. Make sure
you properly file everything, your
taxes. You you do not want to get in
trouble with the government. Make sure
you do not get in trouble with the law
regarding anything. You know, you could
be at a bar getting into a fight and
suddenly that person turns out to be a
government employee got hurt and you're
going to jail. Things like that happen.
And Rahu, when let's say Rahu is in
conjunction, your father's health, you
must look at your father's health. It
doesn't matter actually if your son is
just badly placed. Whether if it's Rahu,
Ketu or Saturn, take your dad before
that dash comes and do a full checkup.
see how everything is doing with him and
do your own health check. Okay? And do
your cholesterol check with uh sun. And
uh one major thing you also got to
remember is that you could be in danger
of losing your position or wherever you
are because if sun is damaged, sun
represents authority. Sun represents you
being at a higher level. So in that
sixth period something might happen
where suddenly you lose your executive
um title and you're suddenly demoted in
your company or you suddenly you get
fired or get laid off. Your father's
business suffers. You know suddenly you
take over the business and uh the father
business starts getting losses or the
business is doing well. However, you're
not making any money. You don't get as
much profit as you wish you know you
had. Let's say if sun is with Saturn or
any maleific planet for that case, you
get into a lot of bickering with your
father. You get into a lot of arguments
and you may suffer a bad relationship
with your father in that case especially
in that dasha you know because son
represents your father the fatherly
figure. So guys this was my analysis on
the sasha
and what happens when you're going
through a certain dasha what are the
major thing that you can expect okay and
obviously the aspects the conjunction of
sun also makes a huge difference as to
what you will experience in these dashas
but if you're new to my channel hey
you're finding out the most important
important part of astrology the most
important part without it you cannot do
any predictions and so if you're new
here subscribe above because I'm going
to be showing you all the planetary
touchas and what happens during the time
period. If you want to know more about
this astrology thing, check out my link
below. Check out my book there,
astrology at the speed of light. You
will love it. Otherwise, I'm going to
see you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
[Music]